var questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      "A - JavaScript is is complementary to and integrated with HTML",
      "B - JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
      "C - Both of the above",
      "D - All of the above",
    ],
    correct: "B - JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 3 - Which of the following type of variable is visible only within a function where it is defined?",
    answers: [
      "A - global variable",
      "B - local variable",
      "C - Both of the above.",
      "D - None of the above",
    ],
    correct: "B - local variable",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 4 - Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
    answers: [
      "A - toExponential()",
      "B - toFixed()",
      "C - toPrecision()",
      "D - toLocaleString()",
    ],
    correct: "B - toFixed()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 5 - Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
    answers: [
      "A - charAt()",
      "B - charCodeAt()",
      "C - concat()",
      "D - indexOf()",
    ],
    correct: "B - charCodeAt()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 6 - Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating whether a reference string comes before or after or is the same as the given string in sort order?",
    answers: [
      "A - localeCompare()",
      "B - search()",
      "C - substr()",
      "D - concat()",
    ],
    correct: "A - localeCompare()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 7 - Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
    answers: [
      "A - toLocaleLowerCase()",
      "B - toLowerCase()",
      "C - toString()",
      "D - substring()",
    ],
    correct: "B - toLowerCase()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 8 - Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?",
    answers: [
      "A - fixed()",
      "B - fontcolor()",
      "C - fontsize()",
      "D - italics()",
    ],
    correct: "D - italics()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 9 - Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
    answers: ["A - pop()", "B - push()", "C - join()", "D - map()"],
    correct: "A - pop()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Q 10 - Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
    answers: [
      "A - toSource()",
      "B - splice()",
      "C - toString()",
      "D - unshift()",
    ],
    correct: "A - toSource()",
  },
  {
    question: "Q 2 - Can you assign a anonymous function to a variable?",
    answers: [
      "A - true",
      "B - false",
      "C - only if it is one line long.",
      "D - all functions are anonymous",
    ],
    correct: "A - true",
  },
];
